[{"answer": "It seems that everywhere I go these days people are talking on their cel", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": "at the grocery store, at restaurantseverywhere", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 14, "question": "It seems that everywhere I go these days people are talking on their cel", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Thats just how it is nowadays, Meghan.  People have the ability to talk whereve", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 16, "question": "at the grocery store, at restaurantseverywhere", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " But its so annoying.  It drives me crazy.  I mean, cant people jus", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Thats just how it is nowadays, Meghan.  People have the ability to talk whereve", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Youre talking like an old man", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 24, "question": " But its so annoying.  It drives me crazy.  I mean, cant people jus", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " I really dont want to hear all of the personal details that someone is sharin", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 25, "question": " Youre talking like an old man", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " You sound just like dad.  Which reminds me, let me tell you about what happene", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 29, "question": " I really dont want to hear all of the personal details that someone is sharin", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": "  What happened", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 33, "question": " You sound just like dad.  Which reminds me, let me tell you about what happene", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " Well dad and I went out to eat at that new restaurant, the kind of fancy on", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 37, "question": "  What happened", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " So what happened", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Well dad and I went out to eat at that new restaurant, the kind of fancy on", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " We were eating and enjoying our food, and everything was going fun.  But th", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 42, "question": " So what happened", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " So", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 46, "question": " We were eating and enjoying our food, and everything was going fun.  But th", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " So, at the table next to us there was a guy, and he took out his cell phone an", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 47, "question": " So", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Really?  Could you hear what he was saying", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 51, "question": " So, at the table next to us there was a guy, and he took out his cell phone an", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Yes, he was only a few inches away from us.  We could hear everything ver", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Really?  Could you hear what he was saying", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Oh, no.  Dad hates that.  What did he do", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Yes, he was only a few inches away from us.  We could hear everything ver", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " At first he didnt do anything.  But then when the guy hung up the phone he di", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 57, "question": " Oh, no.  Dad hates that.  What did he do", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " What did he do", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 61, "question": " At first he didnt do anything.  But then when the guy hung up the phone he di", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " He leaned over to the guy and said, Thanks for talking on your phone here at th", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 62, "question": " What did he do", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " Oh my god.  I would have been so embarassed.  How did the guy react", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 66, "question": " He leaned over to the guy and said, Thanks for talking on your phone here at th", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " He just blushed and said sorry or something", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 67, "question": " Oh my god.  I would have been so embarassed.  How did the guy react", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Well, dad was right.  Thats so rude to talk on your cell phone at a nic", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 68, "question": " He just blushed and said sorry or something", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " It was kind of rude.  But honestly, it wasnt bothering us that much.  Dad didn", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Well, dad was right.  Thats so rude to talk on your cell phone at a nic", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " I would have been embarrassed too.  I agree with dad that it was annoying", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 76, "question": " It was kind of rude.  But honestly, it wasnt bothering us that much.  Dad didn", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " See, you are just like dad", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 80, "question": " I would have been embarrassed too.  I agree with dad that it was annoying", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " But dont you think that the guy was wrong to do that?  Youre at a nic", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 81, "question": " See, you are just like dad", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " I guess", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 88, "question": " But dont you think that the guy was wrong to do that?  Youre at a nic", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " Was it an emergency?  Was he talking about something serious", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 89, "question": " I guess", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " No, it was just small talk", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Was it an emergency?  Was he talking about something serious", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " People are just so used to talking constantly on the phone these days tha", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 91, "question": " No, it was just small talk", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " I guess you have a point", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 95, "question": " People are just so used to talking constantly on the phone these days tha", "qSentId": 94},{"answer": " Thank you.  Talking on the cell phone in public really is an annoying habit", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 96, "question": " I guess you have a point", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": " Remind me not to do it around you next time we go out", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 97, "question": " Thank you.  Talking on the cell phone in public really is an annoying habit", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " Oh, dont worry.  Ill have no problem saying something to you", "docId": "02-08", "aSentId": 98, "question": " Remind me not to do it around you next time we go out", "qSentId": 97}]
